Guide to the Huffington and allied families' papers, 1650-1955 MS 883
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Huffington and allied families' papers
1650-1955
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Huffington, Phyllis Gough
MS 883
17 Linear Feet (14 boxes)
This collection includes biographical sketches, legal documents, books, correspondence, and news clippings about individuals related to the Huffington, Coulbourn, Michel, Gough, Brown, Carrington families, and along with other collateral families. The bulk of the collection pertains to Phyllis Gough Huffington's research into collateral family lines and focuses from the mid-seventeenth century to the mid-twentieth century.
Biographical Note
Richard Huffington Sr. was born in England, in 1656 and supposed to have immigrated to the United States at the age of sixteen imported by Richard Bayley in 1672. A record from the Upper Northampton Court of Accomack, Virginia attests to this importation. He was a long time resident of the area as many depositions and tax lists indicate his inhabitation. He married Mary Windham (believed to be born between 1654 and 1656) in the year of 1679. Together they parented John Huffington Sr. (1680-1749), Richard Huffington Jr. (1693-1756), Susanna Huffington Brown (1694-date of death unknown) and Thomas Huffington (1697-1762). Though his burial place is unknown, it is believed that he died in the year of 1720 in Nanticoke One Hundred, Somerset County, Maryland.
James Brown was born in Virginia, his exact date of birth is unknown, but it is supposed that he was born in the year of 1760. He served as a private in the American Revolutionary War at the age of sixteen. He enlisted on October 2, 1776 while living in Charlotte County, Virginia and served for a total of three years. During his lifetime he was married twice, first to Frances Warren Brown, with whom he had two children Russell Brown (1782-1843), and Frances W. Brown Hancock. Later he would marry Martha (Pattie) Venable Brown on December 13, 1787 in Prince Edward County, Virginia. She would later receive a widow pension from the Bureau of Pensions in 1838 and lived to collect it for a decade. James Brown had passed away on December 16, 1829 in Charlotte County, Virginia.
Henry W. Gough was born in Blaina, Aberystruth Parish, Monmouthshire County, England on December 7, 1861. Biographical sketches indicate that Gough immigrated to the United States in 1863. However, a 1910 Census indicates that Gough immigrated to the States in 1864. For the rest of his life, he was a citizen of Dauphin County, Pennsylvania. On August 25, 1885 he wed Sarah Jane (Jennie) Cope (1860-1925) in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. For nearly a quarter century, Gough served as the County Controller for Dauphin County and had a notable career. He was also a prominent member of the Oddfellow, Masonic, and Elk lodges of Harrisburg. He died on August 27, 1937 and buried three days later in the Harrisburg Cemetery.
Phyllis Gough Huffington was the daughter of Celeste Brown Gough and Captain John Edwin Gough. She was born on January 4, 1923 in the Schofield Barracks on the island of Oahu. She attended Southern Methodist University and earned a Bachelors of Business Administration in 1941. In 1945 she married Roy M. Huffington in Dallas, Texas. Later when the family relocated to Houston Mrs. Huffington was a socially active member of the area's society, in clubs such as the Doctor's Club of Houston and the Petroleum Club of Houston. Other areas that held her interest included genealogy and civic activities, which is apparent by her membership in groups such as the Society of Genealogists (United Kingdom) and the Campfire Girls. Mrs. Huffington passed away on November 9, 2003.
Scope and Contents
The Huffington and Allied Families Papers, 1650-1955 contains materials pertaining to direct ancestors and descendants of Phyllis Gough Huffington and Roy M. Huffington as well as oblique family lines. The collection consists largely of printed materials such as correspondence between Mrs. Huffington and other family members interested in genealogy as well as independent research conducted by Mrs. Huffington. Many of the printed materials include censuses, court proceedings, obituaries, and other news clippings to provide evidence of familial relationships. Other materials include maps, photographs of family members, and certificates.
Access Restriction
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
This material was donated by Terry Huffington, Michael Huffington, and Ralph Dittman in February 2013.
Arrangement
These papers are arranged by original order with descendants largely at the beginning of the series and ancestors towards the end. Research materials have been arranged as discovered with the exception of the oversize materials which were arranged chronologically with respect to original creation date rather than their research dates.
Related Materials
Please refer to Roy M. Huffington Personal and Professional papers,1972-2009, MS 688; Roy M. Huffington Naval Papers, 1942-2005 MS 611 for more information on the Navy and Mr. Huffington; Huffington Oil company records, 1977-2006 MS 575; as well as Roy M. Huffington Ambassadorial Papers, 1988-2008 MS 617.
Index Terms
Subjects
Social life and customs; American Revolution (United States: 1775-1783); Genealogy; War of 1812 (United States: 1812-1815); Emigration and immigration
Document Types
Correspondence
Places
Delaware -- Sussex County; Virginia--Mecklenburg County; Virginia--Charlotte County
Subjects (Persons)
Huffington, John, Jr.; Kellam, Betty; Huffington, William, Sr.; Huffington, Susanna Coulbourn; Michel, Jacob; Brown, Russell; Brown, Sophia Marks; Brown, James Sydnor; Brown, Burwell; Gough, John Edwin
- Series I: Huffington Family
  - Roy M. Huffington and C. Phyllis Gough Huffington, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stassinopolous Documentation, 1986-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Roy Mackey Huffington and Bertha Michel Huffington, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Joseph M. Huffington and Julia Alice Mackey Huffington, 1977-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mackey Documentation, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Ellis Huffington, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emma Taylor Huffington, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harriet Louise Henderson Mackey, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jesse S. Huffington, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hoffecker Documentation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Joel Mackey Jr. and Martha Orr Mackey, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - James Huffington and Susan Coverdale Huffington, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Coverdale Documentation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - William B. Henderson and Margaret Mary Barry Henderson, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - John Barry and Elizabeth Watson Barry, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Laws Documentation, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ann (Nancy) Huffington Outten and Purnell Outten, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Carlisle Documentation, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Silas Huffington, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Captain John C. Huffington and John Huffington, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - William Huffington and Susanna Coulbourn Huffington, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - William Huffington Bradley Sr., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Esther (Easter) Huffington Badley and Thomas Badley, 1986-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Carmichael Documentation, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Acworth Documentation, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - John Huffington Jr. and Betty Kellam Huffington, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Records and Tully Documentation, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - James Nicholson, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Captain Andrew Barry, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Waller Documentation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Luke Huffington, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Colonel Levin Huffington, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - William Coulbourn and Temperance Coulbourn, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Richard Huffington and Mary Windham Huffington, 1993-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Randall Revell, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Robert Houston Huffington, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - William Fletcher Huffington, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - William C. Huffington, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Parker Topping and Amelia Huffington Topping, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Wilton Wilson and Amanda Huffington Wilson, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Charles Easum and Martha Huffington Easum, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Obediah Outten and Elizabeth Huffington Outten, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - William Wonnell and Elizabeth Huffington Wonnell, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Mitchell K. Cathell and Jane Huffington Cathell, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Keene Family Documentation, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Jesse Huffington and Mary Rouxlein Sheilds Huffington, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Sheilds and Dixon Documentation, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - James Pinckney Henderson, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Huffington Civil Registration Certificates, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous Huffington Research Notes, 1993-2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous Huffington Military Documentation, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Virginia: Index to Topographic and Other Map Coverage, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Maryland, Delaware, and District of Columbia: Index to Topographic and Other Map Coverage, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - York and district, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Scarborough, Bridlington, and Holderness district, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - McLean County, Illinois Records, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Clark County, Illinois Records, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jasper County and Lawrence County, Indiana Records, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Yorkshire-St. Crux, England, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Somerset County, Maryland Records, Wills, and Deeds, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Somerset County, Maryland Land Records and Notes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sussex County, Delaware Records and Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sussex County, Delaware Deeds and Orphan Court Records, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Huffington-Eagan Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Huffington Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ernest J. Huffington Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - John Huffington Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sylvester Huffington Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Badley Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - William Huffington Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cooper Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Huffington, Carlisle, and Blizzard Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jesse Huffington and Mary Rouxlein Sheilds Huffington Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Acworth, Carmichael, and Tully Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Carlisle Correspondence, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Mackeys (Variously Spelled) and Allied Families, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Huffington Family History Volume 1, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Huffington Family History Volume 2, circa 1970s (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mary (Barry) and William Barry Henderson, Their Forebears and Descendants, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Descendants of John Huffington, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Ancestors and Descendants of Jonathan Huffington Jr. and Henrietta Adams Huffington, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Delaware Resources, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Maryland Resources, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Resources, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Huffington Research Journal #1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Huffington Research Journal #2, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Huffington Research Journal #3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Huffington Research Journal #4, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Series II: Michel Family
  - Michel Family Pedigree Chart, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jacob (Jake) Michel and Martha Weirich Michel, 1985-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Adam Michel and Elizabeth Reitz Michel, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Johannes Michel, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - George Michel, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Johan Jost Michel, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Catharina Theiss Michel, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Christian Weyrich and Wilhelmina Jochem Weyrich, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Anna Margaretha Wagener Muller, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Annna Margaretha Schnatz Michel, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Anna Thom Wagner and Johannes Wagner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Johan Jost Heinzel and Catherina Theiss Heinzel, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Michel Research Notes, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Deed Records 1831-1953, developed circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Salem Lutheran Church Records and Related Materials, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Series III: Gough Family
  - William Brown Gough, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Celeste Brown Gough, 1987-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - John Edwin Gough, 1967-1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Mary Gough Rubin and Harry Rubin, 1979-1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Henry W. Gough and Jennie L. Cope Gough, 1967-2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - William Gough and Elizabeth Thomas Gough, 1967-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ellen Gough McCrory and John McCrory, 1987-2002 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Price Documentation, 1984-2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Cope Documentation, 1986-2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Lewis and Taylor Documentation, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Cope Tombstone Research, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - St. Paul's Church Records, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ann Thomas Ginbey and James Ginbey, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Goughs of Kittanning, Pennsylvania, 1985-2003 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Thomas Gough and Eleanor Jeffries Gough, 1981-1995 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Jones and Gough Documentation, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Powell and Gough Documentation, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Clarke and Price Documentation, 1963-2003 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Roderick and Gough Documentation, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Gough Research Notes, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Wales and England Resources, 1 of 2, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Wales and England Resources, 2 of 2, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Pennsylvania Resources, 1987-1998 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Gough Research Journal, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Series IV: Brown Family
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Application for C. Phyllis Gough Huffington, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Application Evidence, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution papers for C. Phyllis Gough Huffington, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Application for Terry Huffington Dittman, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Marie Hook Brown Lyle and George Dorriss Brown, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - John Duval Hook and Elizabeth Jane Carrington Hook, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Zadok Hook Sr. and Mary Elizabeth West Hook, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth Johnson Hook, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - John Duval West and Christina Summit West, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - West Documentation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - James Hook and Cynthia Ann Summit Hook, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - George Summit, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - William Hook and Madeline Turner Hook, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mary Hook Turner and Henry Turner, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Thomas Hook and Sally Long Hook, 1970-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Belitha Hook Sr. and William Hook Sr., 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Roger Hook Sr. and Jeremiah Hook Sr., 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Callaway County, Missouri 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Callaway County, Missouri 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Callaway County and other counties, Missouri, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Worcester County, Maryland 1 of 2, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Worcester County, Maryland 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Maryland Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Analysis of censuses and related materials of Missouri Counties, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Boone, Bracken, and Miscellaneous Counties, Kentucky, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Nicholas County, Kentucky, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Pendleton County, Kentucky, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hampshire County, West Virginia, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Notes on Texas Hook family members, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Bartholomew County, Indiana, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Paul D. Carrington and Bessie Meek Carrington, 1989-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Paul Carrington and Frances DeWitt Carrington, 1982-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - William T. Carrington and Mary Holloway Carrington, 1990-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Davis and Whanger Documentation, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Judge William Carrington and Susan Clark Fisher Carrington, 1990-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fisher and Humphreys Documentation, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Yocum and McGary Documentation, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Samuel Carrington, 1973-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - John Carrington, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Timothy Carrington, 1980-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annie B. Dorriss Halderman and Joseph A. Halderman, 1952-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General George P. Dorriss and Sarah Henderson Dorriss, 1973-2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Martin W. Dorriss, circa 1980s (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Felix Grundy Dorriss, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Thomas M. Dorriss, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Reverend Joseph Dorris, 1986-2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Halderman and Athana Documentation, 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Frances (Fanny) Brown Weiss, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Joseph A. Brown and Martha Dorriss Brown Whisker, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - James Sydnor Brown and Melinda Cochran Brown, 1971-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cochran Documentation, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Russell Brown and Sophia Marks Brown, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sydnor and Marks Documentation, 1977-2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Glenn and Hancock Documentation, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - James Brown, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Phoebe Bonner Brown, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Burwell Brown Sr. and Amy Freeman Brown, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - William Brown and Mary Brown, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Russell Brown and Elizabeth Brown, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - North Documentation, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Brown-Williamson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Lyle Documentation, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Mosher Documentation, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Reade, Lewis, Warner, and Martiau Documentation, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Jones, Barber, and Timson Documentation, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Macon and Woodward Documentation, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Archer Documentation, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bolling and Epps Documentation, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Henderson, Hudson, Isham, and Randolph Documentation, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Brown Research Notes, 1 of 3, 1973-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Brown Research Notes, 2 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Brown Research Notes, 3 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - A History of the Pioneer Families of Missouri, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Shrine of the Ozarks: A history of Southwest Missouri State College 1905-1965, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Brown Research Journal #1, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Brown Research Journal #2, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brown Research Journal #3, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brown Research Journal #4, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brown Research Journal #5, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brown Research Journal #6, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brown Research Journal #7, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Missouri Resources, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Resources, 1996-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Resources, 1992-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Niles Weekly Register" 1814-1815 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - National Genealogical Society Conferences, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Society of Genealogists Membership, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - State Historical Society of Missouri, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution Membership materials, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Research Forms (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Genealogical Research Contacts (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Series V: Oversize
  General
  These materials are copies of primary sources that largely pertain to the Huffington line (Boxes 7-9 and boxes 11-13) but Box 10 exclusively houses primary source copies for the Brown line. Box 14 consists of photographs and certificates of family members from both Mr. and Mrs. Huffington's lines.
  - Deed of Sale from William Huffington to John Coulbourn, 1778, Undated (Box 7, Item 1)
  - 1800 Census of Broadcreek Ten, Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - 1810 Census of Cecil County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 3)
  - 1820 Census of Kent County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 4)
  - 1820-1840 Censuses of Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - 1840 Census of Vienna District, Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - 1840 Census of Delaware, Undated (Box 7, Item 7)
  - 1850 Census of Washington Township, Buchanan County, Missouri, 1998 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - 1850 Census of Locust Ward, Philadelphia County, Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - 1850 Census of Baltimore County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 10)
  - 1850 Census of Third Ward, Baltimore, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 11)
  - 1850 Census of Nanticoke One Hundred, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 7, Item 12)
  - 1850 Census of Marion County, Indiana, Undated (Box 7, Item 13)
  - 1850-1860 Censuses of Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 7, Item 14)
  - 1850 Census of Duck Creek One Hundred, Kent County, Delaware, Undated (Box 7, Item 15)
  - 1850 Census of Dorchester County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 16)
  - 1860 Census of Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 17)
  - 1860 Census of Pasquotank County, North Carolina, Undated (Box 7, Item 18)
  - 1860 Census of Third Ward, Baltimore County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 7, Item 19)
  - 1860 Census of Lawrence County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Civil War Cards, Confederate, Undated (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Pension Cards, 1864-1922, Undated (Box 7, Item 22)
  - 1870 Census of Sixth Ward, Baltimore City, Maryland, 1998 (Box 7, Item 23)
  - 1870 Census of Franklin Township, Marion County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 7, Item 24)
  - 1900 Census Index of Dorchester County, Maryland, Undated (Box 7, Item 25)
  - 1910 Census of Norfolk City, Virginia, Undated (Box 7, Item 26)
  - 1910 Census of Greenwich Township, Connecticut, Undated (Box 7, Item 27)
  - 1910 Census of Fairfield County, Connecticut, Undated (Box 7, Item 28)
  - 1810 Census of Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - 1810 Census of Broadcreek, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 8, Item 2)
  - 1810 Census of Nanticoke One Hundred, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 8, Item 3)
  - 1820-1830 Censuses of Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 8, Item 4)
  - 1830 Census of Kent County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - 1830-1850 Censuses of Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 8, Item 6)
  - 1840 Census of Second Ward, Baltimore City, Maryland, Undated (Box 8, Item 7)
  - 1850 Census of Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - 1850 Census of Barren Creek District, Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 9)
  - 1850 Census of District Number One, Dorchester County, Maryland, Undated (Box 8, Item 10)